streamzoo.com 2011-10-16

# Streamzoo - Privacy Policy

**PHONEZOO COMMUNICATIONS, INC. PRIVACY POLICY**

We at Phonezoo Communications, Inc. ("Phonezoo," "we," "us," "our") know that our users ("you," "your") care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy for streamzoo.com. **By visiting or using the Streamzoo.com website and domain name, and any other linked pages, features, content, or any other services we offer from time to time by in connection therewith (collectively, the "Website"), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways.**

I. WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we gather when you are accessing or using our Website. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage. ****

We do not knowingly collect or solicit Personal Information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Website or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on the Website. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [**privacy@streamzoo.com**](mailto:privacy@streamzoo.com). 

II. WHAT INFORMATION DOES PHONEZOO COLLECT?

We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained more fully below. We may use this Personal Information to personalize and improve our services, to allow our users to set up a user account and profile, to contact users, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to analyze how users utilize the Website, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may share certain types of Personal Information with third parties (as set forth in this Section and in Section III below). We collect the following types of information: 

**A. Information You Provide to Us:**

We receive and store any information you provide to us. For example, we collect Personal Information such as your name, email address, IP address, browser information, mobile photos and videos, and third-party account credentials (for example, your log-in credentials for Facebook or other third party sites if you've logged in through such a site). If you provide your third-party account credentials to us, you understand some content and/or information in those accounts ("Third Party Account Information"), may be transmitted into your account with us if your authorize such transmissions, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Website is covered by this Privacy Policy. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to register with us or take advantage of many of our special features. 

**B. Information Collected Automatically:**

  * Whenever you interact with our Website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, "cookie" information, and the page you requested. "Cookies" are identifiers we transfer to your computer through your browser that allow us to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser to prevent or limit your computer's acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of our Website's best features. Our advertising partners may also transmit cookies to your computer, when you click on ads that appear on our site. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 
  * We also collect usage information, including without limitation the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site. We only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, this aggregate data tells us how often customers use parts of the Website, so that we can make the Website appealing to as many customers as possible. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners, so that they can understand how often people use their services and our Website, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal online experience. We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally. 

**C. E-mail and Other Communications:**

We may contact you, by email or other means; for example, we may send you promotional offers on behalf of other businesses, or communicate with you about your use of the Website. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please change your account settings accordingly. Also, we may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. This confirmation helps us make emails more interesting and improve our service. 

III. WILL PHONEZOO SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES? 

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We share your Personal Information in personally identifiable form with third parties only as described below. 

**A. Affiliated Businesses and Third Party Websites We Do Not Control:** In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we're affiliated with may sell items or provide services to you through the Website (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your Personal Information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service. One such service may include the ability for you to choose to automatically transmit Third Party Account Information to your Website profile, or from your Website profile to your third party account. We have no control over the policies and practices of third party websites as to privacy or anything else, so if you choose to allow these automatic transmissions, please review all third party websites' policies. 

**B. Agents:** We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. 

**C. User Profiles and Submissions:** __ Certain user profile information, including without limitation a user's name, email address, and mobile photos and videos, may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Website or address your request for Company's services. Your account privacy settings allow you to limit the other users who can see the Personal Information in your user profile and/or what information in your user profile is visible to others. Any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your public profile page, as part of a product review, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your user name may be displayed to other users if and when you send messages or comments or upload images or videos through the Website and other users can contact you through messages and comments. 

**D. Business Transfers:** We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Also, if we (or substantially all of our assets) are acquired, or if we are reorganized or go through some other change of control (including without limitation going into bankruptcy), Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. 

**E. Protection of Phonezoo and Others:** We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Phonezoo, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**F. With Your Consent:** Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information. 

IV. IS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE? 

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. If you access your account via a third party site or service, you may have additional or different sign-on protections via that third party site or service. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-on mechanism appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account. 

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

The Website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site's privacy policy. 

V. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS? 

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, change or delete the following information you've provided to us: 

  * Username and password 
  * Email address 
  * User profile information 

The information you can view and update may change as the Website changes. If you delete your account, any public comments you have made on the website will not be deleted, and will remain visible to others. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at [**privacy@streamzoo.com**](mailto:privacy@streamzoo.com). 

VI. WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE? 

  * You can always opt not to disclose information to us or on the Website, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our special features. 
  * You may be able to add, update, or delete certain information as explained in Section V above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. You may request deletion of your account by [**support@streamzoo.com**](mailto:support@streamzoo.com). Please note that some information may remain in our private records after your deletion of such information from your account. Please also note that when you delete your account, any public comments you have made on the Website will not be deleted, and will remain visible to others. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you delete your information, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. 
  * If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, please change your account settings accordingly. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us via email, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. 

VII. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Website after such changes have been first posted. 

VIII. QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message to [**privacy@streamzoo.com**](mailto:privacy@streamzoo.com). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns. 

_Effective Date: February 24th, 2011_
